http://www.albionsaddlemakers.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Search for a product
Albion England Your Account Search
View Bag
No products in the basket.
HomeequestrianBridlesKB BridlesComplete HeadstallsPadded HeadpiecesSlipsCheeksBrowbandsNosebandsReinsBridle ComponentsSaddlesDressageJumpGPSaddle VerificationAccessoriesGirthsLeathersMartingales/BreastplatesHead Collars/Lead ChainsNumnahsBandagesSaddle ProtectionLeather CareStirrup IronsSportingLifestyleBeltsCroc BeltHatch BeltAccessoriesLuxury CandlesUmbrellasDog CollarsDog LeadsSilk ScarvesCashmere ScarvesHandbagsThe AmaleaThe AdorabellaThe AmoritaOlivia Clutch BagAnna Clutch BagSaleBlog
FREE UK DELIVERY ON ALL ORDERS OVER £50
Privacy PolicyThis page will be regularly updated to show you all the things we do with your personal data. This policy applies if you’re a client, supplier, partner and an employee.EMPLOYEES SHOULD ALSO READ OUR DATA PROTECTION POLICY.About Albion EnglandAlbion England is located at Albion England, Albion House, Bridgeman Street, Walsall, WS2 9PG, England. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.Things covered in the privacy policy:What information we collect about you? How will we use this information about you? Marketing Access to your information and correction1 Cookies Other websites Changes to our privacy policy How to contact usWhat information do we collect about you?Your personal data is any information which identifies you, or which can be identified as relating to you personally for example, name, address, phone number, email address that may be collected and used by us. We’ll only collect the personal data that we need.We collect information about you when you contact us via phone, email or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and use offers. Website usage information is collected using cookies so we are able to provide users with a better experience.The personal data you give us may include name, title, address, employment status, demographic information, email address, telephone numbers, personal description, photographs, CCTV images, attitudes, opinions, usernames and passwords.How will we use the information about you?We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, with your consent, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you. We will only process your personal data for legitimate purposes as set by the General Data Protection Regulations (from 25th May 2018).Albion England will not share your information for marketing purposes with other companies, we will only share your details with organisations when necessary in order to fulfil our service to you and where the privacy and security of your data is assured. In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.MarketingWe would like to send you information about our products and services and other companies in our group which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have the right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes.Access to your information and correctionYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email sales@albionengland.co.uk or write to us at the following address, Albion England, Albion House, Bridgeman Street, Walsall, WS2 9PG, England for the attention of Data Officer. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.CookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.This website uses the following Cookies: Google Analytics: This cookie allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on the website. The information is depersonalised and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using Google Analytics we can what content is popular on our website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching.For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.Other websitesOur website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to our website you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies. We are not liable for the information provided through these links.Changes to our privacy policyWe keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 26th July 2018. We are required by law to provide any information we hold to fraud agencies, the police or government agencies when summoned to do so.How to contact usPlease contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or the information we hold about you:By Email: sales@albionengland.co.uk Write to us: Albion England, Albion House, Bridgeman Street, Walsall, WS2 9PG, England
+44 (0) 1922 646 210sales@albionengland.co.uk
InfoCOVID-19About UsBespoke ServiceThe Choice of ChampionsAlbion Tree DesignBridle FittingTestimonialsFollow AlbionStockistsBecome an Albion StockistJob VacanciesDelivery & ReturnsWarranty RegistrationWarranty InformationPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsContact My AccountMy AccountCheckoutShopping Bag Contact AlbionCall: +44 (0) 1922 646 210Email: sales@albionengland.co.uk Head Office (UK):
Albion England Albion House Bridgeman Street Walsall WS2 9PG England
Subscribe to NewsletterSubscribe to Albion updates to receive latest news, events & offersSubscribe
About UsThe Choice of ChampionsAlbion Tree DesignBespoke ServiceBridle FittingStockistsBecome an Albion StockistTestimonialsDelivery & ReturnsSaddle VerificationWarranty RegistrationWarranty InformationFollow AlbionContact
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience. By continuing to use the website you accept their use. Please read our Privacy Policy.OK I AGREE...
